let questions = [
    {
        question: "What is the (unofficial) name of this Vehicle:",
        answer: 1,
        options: [
            "Silver Wind",
            "Spruce goose",
            "The Cloud",
            "Swimming Elephant"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "What be the name of this fine vessel?",
        answer: 0,
        options: [
            "Boaty mc'boat face",
            "Smilling grandpa",
            "Ray of sunshine",
            "Poor mans Naming convention"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Which Country was the experimental Aerotrain developed in?",
        answer: 3,
        options: [
            "Germany",
            "America",
            "Japan",
            "France"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Which one of These is Not part of the shinkansen L0 Series?",
        answer: 3,
        options: [
            "Aerobrakes",
            "Seismic Sensors",
            "Magnets",
            "Wheels"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "What was the use of the ship Calypso, under Jacques Cousteau?",
        answer: 2,
        options: [
            "Minesweeping",
            "Oil Surveying",
            "Oceonographic research",
            "Art trading"
        ]
    },


    {
        question: "How long was this ships longest journey?",
        answer: 0,
        options: [
            "1,3 km",
            "13 km",
            "130 km",
            "1300 km"
        ]
    },

    {
        question: "What are the 2 pillars on the Alcyone?",
        answer: 0,
        options: [
            "Turbosails",
            "Satelite launchers",
            "Long Range Radars",
            "360-Degree Infared Cameras"
        ]
    },


    {
        question: "What are the 2 pillars on this rotor ship used for?",
        answer: 2,
        options: [
            "Oil rig Relocation",
            "Underwater construction",
            "Propulsion",
            "Astronomy"
        ]
    },

    {
        question: "What is the research achievment of this airplane?",
        answer: 3,
        options: [
            "No pilot needed",
            "No energy needed",
            "No satelite guidance",
            "No moving parts"
        ]
    },


    {
        question: "The deepsea challanger went to:",
        answer: 1,
        options: [
            "Point Nemo",
            "Challenger deep",
            "Denmark Strait Cataract",
            "Lake Chad"
        ]
    },


    {
        question: "The bathyscaphe Archimede had a joint expedition with Cyana and DSV Alvin where?",
        answer: 3,
        options: [
            "Mediteranian coastline",
            "Mount everest",
            "Indian Ocean",
            "Mid-Atlantic Ridge"
        ]
    },


    {
        question: "The Nereus:",
        answer: 2,
        options: [
            "Is orange",
            "Smeels like chocolate",
            "Is imploded",
            "Can fly"
        ]
    },

];